"lang"
{
	"Language" "English"
	"Tokens"
	{
		"TipLabel"							"Tip!"
		"LoadingMap"						"Deploying to:"

		// Note: When making tips, it is possible to display the currently bound button of a command
		//		 using the following syntax: %command%
		//		 For example, "Use %duck% to crouch!" becomes "Use <CTRL> to crouch!" if "+duck" is bound to CTRL.
		"TIP_CAPTURE_DEFEND"		"Defending objectives is as important as capturing them."
		"TIP_CAPTURE_FEEDBACK"		"Listen and look for feedback to see a capture zone's status while capping."
		"TIP_CAPTURE_OVERPOWER"		"Capturing a point is always possible as long as you outnumber the enemy."
		"TIP_CAPTURE_SPAWNS"		"Capturing enemy points will cause spawning enemies to start farther away."
		"TIP_CHECK_AMMO"			"Check your equipment after a firefight, you may be low on ammo!"
		"TIP_CHECK_AMMO_BUTTON"		"To check your remaining ammo, press and hold %ammobelt%."
		"TIP_CLIMBING"				"Climb over walls and obstacles using %jump%."
		"TIP_COMMUNICATE"			"Always communicate with your team. Tell them where enemies are."
		"TIP_CROUCH_PRONE"			"The crouch and prone stances will greatly increase your accuracy."
		"TIP_DROP_AMMO"				"You can drop ammo for your fellow soldiers/soldats by pressing %dropammo%."
		"TIP_DROP_AMMO_EXTRA"		"You can drop ammo for your fellow Machine Gunner by pressing %dropextraammo% (Class specific)."
		"TIP_FIRE_IN_BURSTS"		"Fire your MG in bursts; it preserves accuracy, ammo, and prevents overheating."
		"TIP_FRIENDLY_FIRE"			"Friendly fire is on by default. Don't hurt your teammates!"
		"TIP_GRENADE_MG"			"You can clear out enemy MGs with grenades."
		"TIP_GRENADE_ROLL"			"A single press of %attack% after priming your grenade will throw it underhand."
		"TIP_GRENADE_SMOKE"			"Use smoke grenades to cover your advance or to provide a distraction."
		"TIP_GRENADE_STRENGTH"		"The longer you hold %attack% to throw a grenade, the harder it is thrown."
		"TIP_GRENADE_TEAMMATES"		"Be aware of your teammates' positions before throwing grenades."
		"TIP_GRENADE_WINDOW"		"Grenades can break through windows if thrown hard enough."
		"TIP_GROUP_COVER"			"When fighting in a group make sure to use covering fire."
		"TIP_IDENTIFY"				"Make sure you have identified the target as an enemy before firing."
		"TIP_JUMPING"				"Use %jump% to leap while sprinting."
		"TIP_JUMPING_STAMINA"		"Running and jumping will drain your stamina. Stay fit for battle."
		"TIP_LEANING"   			"Leaning around a corner (using %leanleft% and %leanright%) could save your life."
		"TIP_MORALE_RECOVER"		"When your morale is low, regroup with friendlies to quickly recover."
		"TIP_NCO_MORALE"			"Always try to fight alongside your NCO for a morale boost."
		"TIP_PINNED_MORALE"			"Don't get pinned down! An enemy MG shooting over you will hurt your morale."
		"TIP_POINT_GUN"				"When firing a weapon the shooty end goes towards the enemy!"
		"TIP_PRONE_DIVE"			"Pressing prone (%+prone%) while running will send you into a dive."
		"TIP_PRONE_ROLL"			"Pressing a lean (%+leanleft% and %+leanright%) button while prone will make you roll in that direction."
		"TIP_SIGHTS_HOLD"			"You can zoom your sights further by pressing and holding %ironsights%."
		"TIP_SIGHTS_LONGRANGE"		"The full ironsights should generally be used when firing long range."
		"TIP_SPEECH_ENEMY"			"Be careful with in-game speech. The enemy might be listening!"
		"TIP_SQUADS"				"Enemies also use squads. Where there is one enemy there are probably more!"
		"TIP_TACTICS_COVER"			"Hedgerows, foliage and impact holes make great cover and camouflage."
		"TIP_TACTICS_COVER2"		"Avoid open fields. While advancing, move from cover to cover."
		"TIP_TACTICS_FLANKING"		"Use Squad tactics. Flanking maneuvers can be very helpful."
		"TIP_TACTICS_FLANKING2"		"The shortest route to an objective is often the most dangerous. Use flanks!"
		"TIP_TACTICS_FLANKING3"		"Prevent the enemy from flanking you. Cover all sides."
		"TIP_TACTICS_MG_COVER"		"As an MG, ask for at least one rifleman to cover your back and flanks."
		"TIP_TEAM_STRENGTH"			"Team up with every friendly soldier you find. Strength comes in numbers."
		"TIP_USE_MAP"				"Utilize your map! Knowing the battlefield is very important."
		"TIP_WAIT_FOR_MORE"			"Sometimes it is best to wait in spawn for more reinforcements."
		"TIP_WEAPON_SUPPRESSION"	"Every weapon can suppress an enemy, not only MGs."
		"TIP_WIN_BY_CAPPING"		"Matches are not won by amount of kills, but by capturing objectives as a team."
	}
}